let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is snap in the Avengers Endgame for the reason of Thanos Death ?",
    answer: "c. Iron Man",
    options: [
      "A. Thanos",
      "B. Hulk",
      "c. Iron Man",
      "D. Thor",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Where is from Captain America ?",
    answer: "A. Brooklyn Newyork",
    options: [
      "A. Brooklyn Newyork",
      "B. Manhattan Newyork",
      "C. Bronx Newyork",
      "D. Queens Newyork",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is the father of tony stark ?",
    answer: "A. Howard stark",
    options: [
      "A. Howard stark",
      "B. Adam stark",
      "C. Stephen stark",
      "D. Stark",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which year loki Attack in the Newyork ?",
    answer: "D. 2012",
    options: [
      "A. 2015",
      "B. 2011",
      "C. 2019",
      "D. 2012",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who's gave idea the time travel concept in the Avengers Endgame ?",
    answer: "D. Scott Lang",
    options: [
      "A. Tony Stark",
      "B. Bruce banner",
      "C. Rocket Racoon",
      "D. Scott Lang"
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who sacrifices themselves for the Soul Stone? ",
    answer: "C. Natasha Romanoff",
    options: [
      "A. Gamora",
      "B. Clint Barton",
      "C. Natasha Romanoff",
      "D. Red Skull"
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who directed Avengers: Endgame?",
    answer: "B. Russo Brother",
    options: [
      "A. James Gonn",
      "B. Russo Brother",
      "C. Jon Watts",
      "D. Jon Favreau"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which Metal use to make a Captain America's Shield ?",
    answer: "A. Vibranium",
    options: [
      "A. Vibranium",
      "B. Uru Metal",
      "C. Titanium",
      "D. Adamantine"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the Head of the S.H.I.E.L.D in the year 2012 ?",
    answer: "C. Colonel Nick Fury",
    options: [
      "A. Antony Edward",
      "B. Colonel Rick Stoner",
      "C. Colonel Nick Fury",
      "D. Steve Rogers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which Metal are Tony Stark use to Make their Suit ?",
    answer: "C. Titanium",
    options: [
      "A. Vibranium",
      "B. Uru Metal",
      "C. Titanium",
      "D. Adamantine"
    ]
  }
];
